{"data":[{"question":"The child labor was made ___ from morning till night in this country.","a":"work","b":"to work","c":"worked","d":"working","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Active voice: make sbd do sth \n- Passive voice: sbd + be made to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The number of the employees in our industry ___ 1 million.","a":"adds up to","b":"have added up to","c":"is added up to","d":"has been added up to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense + active voice \n- The expression the number is followed by a singular verb while the expression a number is followed by a plural verb.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The cat ___ much farther before it caught that mouse up.","a":"was not going","b":"did not go","c":"had not gone","d":"had not been going","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past \n+ Past perfect tense + before simple past tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The TV series is worthy ___ again.","a":"of seeing","b":"to see","c":"seeing","d":"of being seen","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be worthy of sth\/doing sth: to deserve to be thought about or treated in a particular way\n- Passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The surgeon said that the patient had to ___ right now.","a":"operate on","b":"operate","c":"be operated on","d":"be operated","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice: have\/has to + be + PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"I ___ in the heavy rain on my way to the shopping mall.","a":"caught","b":"was caught","c":"had caught","d":"was catching","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past) + passive voice ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"One's success cannot always ___ in terms of money.","a":"to measured","b":"being measured","c":"be measured","d":"to be measured","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice with modal verb (can\/could\/should...): can\/could\/should...+ be + pp","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The lightening ___ the first fire.","a":"may have caused","b":"can't have caused","c":"ought to have caused","d":"should cause","answer":"1","explain":"\n- May have pp: if something may happen or may be true, there is a possibility that it will happen or be true but this is not certain","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Why are you staying at work so late? \"Well, there is a lot of work that ___ by tonight.\"","a":"needs to be finished","b":"must being finished","c":"needs to finish","d":"must to be finished","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice \n- Need + To be Past Participle\/ V_ing: if before \"need\" is not person \n- Need + To Verb: If before \"need\" is person","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"In warm weather food ___ long.","a":"cannot be kept","b":"don't keep","c":"are not keeping","d":"are not kept","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Cannot: used to say that something is impossible or unlikely \n- Passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}